## **BELLO**, Olamide

olacase@gmail.com, linkdin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/olamide-bello-19079830/ 773-502-5236

#### Professional Overview

Experienced System Support Analyst with a great passion for products that make a difference and promote cultural impact. Comfortable using numerous technologies including software / development frameworks Microsoft, MongoDB/JavaScript, SQL and several business ERP's. Goal Driven. Very quick to learn and adapt to new situations.

#### Education

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science | Lagos State University. Full Stack Web Development | Ohio State University

#### Skills

Development: JavaScript, MongoDB, SQL, JQuery, Node.js, React, Express.JS, CSS, HTML, Front End and Back End API's.

Environment: Visual Studio 2015-2003, Visual Studio Code, SQL Server, Eclipse

Source Control: Git, Mercurial, TFS, Perforce

QA/Test: VS Test Tools, Quick Test Professional, Junit

Cloud: Heroku, AWS, Google Cloud

System: Windows Server 2008, 2012, 2016, 2019 proficient, Active Directory, ServiceNow, Opera Hospitality Management

System, Oracle SunSystems Financials, Micros Materials Control, Microsoft Office 365, VMware, EPIC

Network/Security Cisco Meraki, FORTINET, CYBEROAM/SOPHOS, Palo-Alto, SilverPeak, Huawei Network Aggregators

## Career Objective (span of 10 years)

To emerge as the Head of a strategic business unit of such an organization with a leverage to initiate or contribute to strategic change and improve people and process management in the organization, with a view to help the attainment or sustenance of competitive advantage.

#### Philosophy

I can do what you can't do you can do what I can't do; together we can do great things.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

System Analyst | March 2021- April 2022

**Greencore USA** 

### **Job Description**

- ❖ Worked with Customer and End User Support using the ticketing system.
- Supporting end users with application related issues
- Responding to recurring or one-off daily Incident
- System Troubleshooting and Repairs.
- Installation of System hardware and software
- Network Issues Troubleshooting and Support
- Desktop Computer Endpoint installation and maintenance
- Keeping all contracts up to date
- Creation and deletion of end users in the active directory
- tasked with IT service management (ITSM)

System Analyst | Feb 2019- Feb 2021

Outsource LLC.

## **Job Description**

- Information Systems management.
- System Troubleshooting and Repairs.
- Installation of System hardware and software
- Network System Support
- Project Management and Implementation
- Data Support

# Golden Tulip Hotels & Conference Center.

# Job Description

- \* Responsible for Information Systems management, IT Service Management
- \* Responsible for System Troubleshooting and Repairs.
- Maintaining Active Directory
- Resolve ticketing issues and Service Now
- Installation of System hardware and software
- Network System Support
- Project Management and Implementation using Agile technique
- Responsible for Data Support, Backup, and Disaster Recovery testing
- Training users on how to use the business applications

## REFERENCES

To be provided of request.